<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Универсальная Молитва времени</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Параметры</string>
    <string name="prayer_times">Время молитвы</string>
    <string name="lahore">Alaqehdari Deh-e Shu</string>
    <string name="pakistan">Afghanistan</string>
    <string name="qibla_directions">Направление киблы</string>
    <string name="clock_wise">261</string>
    <string name="settings_label">Параметры</string>
    <string name="prefs_menu_title">Параметры</string>
    <string name="about_menu_title">около</string>
    <string name="search_title">поиск</string>
    <string name="screen_down_text">Пожалуйста держите телефон горизонтально и к вверх так что это компас может работать. Не удается определить направление Север</string>
    <string name="no_location_yet">Подождите. Определение вашего местоположения или вы можете выбрать свой город в настройках.</string>
    <string name="geo_location_info">Полученные данные о местоположении.</string>
    <string name="latitude_north">N</string>
    <string name="latitude_south">S</string>
    <string name="longitude_east">E</string>
    <string name="longitude_west">W</string>
    <string name="gps_status">Use GPS</string>
    <string name="gps_status_summary">Enables using GPS for getting your location.</string>
    <string name="gps_prompt">Использование GPS</string>
    <string name="gps_summary">Позволяет использовать GPS для получения вашего местоположения.</string>
    <string name="state_location_title">Задать местоположение вручную</string>
    <string name="state_location_summary">Выберите один из столицы провинции Ирана, если вы находитесь рядом с ними.</string>
    <string name="about_title_text">\nоколо Универсальная Молитва времени</string>
    <string name="about_text">\nAll Rights Reserved</string>

    <!-- Do not translate next two tag, it's used by program for other reasons -->
    <string name="gps_pref_key">GPS_LOCATION_PREF</string>
    <string name="state_location_pref_key">state_LOCATION_PREF</string>
    <string name="release_date">March 30, 2011\n</string>
    <string name="version">Version 1.22</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">SplashActivity</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="prayer_time_now">Это время молитвы сейчас</string>

    <!-- Messages -->
    <string name="exit_message">Вы уверены, вы хотите выйти?</string>
    <string name="ok_string">Да</string>
    <string name="no_string">НЕТ</string>
    <string name="rate_us_string">Оцените нас</string>
    <string name="on_string">ON</string>
    <string name="off_string">OFF</string>

    <!-- Prayer Names -->
    <string name="fajar">Фаджр</string>
    <string name="shrooq">Ишрак</string>
    <string name="zuhur">Зухр</string>
    <string name="asar">Аср</string>
    <string name="maghrib">Магриб</string>
    <string name="isha">Иша</string>

    <!-- Juristics -->
    <string name="title_select_juristic">Выберите юридических</string>
    <string name="hanafi">Ханафи</string>
    <string name="shafii">Шафии</string>
    <string name="malaki">Малаки</string>
    <string name="hanbali">Ханбали</string>

    <!-- Calculation Methods -->
    <string name="title_select_calc_method">Выберите метод расчета</string>
    <string name="jafari">Джафари</string>
    <string name="karachi">Карачи</string>
    <string name="isna">ИСНА</string>
    <string name="mwl">МЖЛ</string>
    <string name="makkah">Мекка</string>
    <string name="egypt">Египет</string>
    <string name="custom">Пользовательские</string>
    <string name="tehran">Тегеран</string>

    <!-- Settings Screen -->
    <string name="country_string">СТРАНА</string>
    <string name="city_string">ГОРОД</string>
    <string name="juristics_string">юридический</string>
    <string name="adhan_audio_string">АЗАН АУДИО</string>
    <string name="calc_method_string">МЕТОД</string>
    <string name="gps_location_string">GPS</string>
    <string name="daylight_saving_string">ЛЕТНЕЕ ВРЕМЯ</string>
    <string name="language_string">язык</string>

    <!-- ToolTip -->
    <string name="like_on_facebook">Как на facebook</string>

    <!-- Time -->
    <string name="hours">часов</string>
    <string name="minutes">протокол</string>
    <string name="after">спустя</string>
    <string name="its">это</string>
    <string name="at">в</string>
    <string name="time">время.</string>

    <!-- Select Language -->
    <string name="title_select_lannguage">Выбор языка</string>

    <!-- Google API -->
    <string name="google_play_services_version">a152a304f4d20ae</string>

    <string name="drawer_open">Slider Menu Opened</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Slider Menu Closed</string>

    <!-- Nav Drawer Menu Items -->
    <string-array name="nav_drawer_items">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Azan</item>
        <item>Kalimas</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
        <item>MoreApps</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="desc_list_item_icon">Item Icon</string>

    <array name="qalma_name_list">
        <item>1st Kalma Tayyibah</item>
        <item>2nd Kalma Shahaadat</item>
        <item>3rd Kalma Tamjeed</item>
        <item>4th Kalma Tawheed</item>
        <item>5th Kalma Astaghfar</item>
        <item>6th Kalma Radd Kufr</item>
    </array>

    <array name="qalma_list">
        <item>لَآ اِلٰهَ اِلَّا اللّٰهُ مُحَمَّدٌ رَّسُوْلُ اللّٰهِؕ</item>
        <item>اَشْهَدُ اَنْ لَّآ اِلٰهَ اِلَّا اللہُ وَحْدَهٗ لَا شَرِيْكَ لَهٗ وَ اَشْهَدُ اَنَّ مُحَمَّدً اعَبْدُهٗ وَرَسُوْلُهٗ</item>
        <item>سُبْحَان اللهِ وَ الْحَمْدُ لِلّهِ وَ لآ اِلهَ اِلّا اللّهُ وَ اللّهُ اَكْبَرُ وَلا حَوْلَ وَلاَ قُوَّة ِ الَّا بِاللّهِ الْعَلِىّ الْعَظِيْم</item>
        <item>لَآ اِلٰهَ اِلَّا اللهُ وَحْدَهٗ لَا شَرِيْكَ لَهٗ لَهُ الْمُلْكُ وَ لَهُ الْحَمْدُ يُحْىٖ وَ يُمِيْتُ وَ هُوَحَیٌّ لَّا يَمُوْتُ اَبَدًا اَبَدًاؕ ذُو الْجَلَالِ وَالْاِكْرَامِؕ بِيَدِهِ الْخَيْرُؕ وَهُوَ عَلٰى كُلِّ شیْ ٍٔ قَدِیْرٌؕ</item>
        <item>اَسْتَغْفِرُ اللهَ رَبِّىْ مِنْ كُلِّ ذَنْۢبٍ اَذْنَبْتُهٗ عَمَدًا اَوْ خَطَا ًٔ سِرًّا اَوْ عَلَانِيَةً وَّاَتُوْبُ اِلَيْهِ مِنَ الذَّنْۢبِ الَّذِیْٓ اَعْلَمُ وَ مِنَ الذَّنْۢبِ الَّذِىْ لَآ اَعْلَمُ اِنَّكَ اَنْتَ عَلَّامُ الْغُيُوْبِ وَ سَتَّارُ الْعُيُوْبِ و َغَفَّارُ الذُّنُوْبِ وَ لَا حَوْلَ وَلَا قُوَّةَ اِلَّا بِاللهِ الْعَلِىِّ الْعَظِيْمِؕ</item>
        <item>اَللّٰهُمَّّ اِنِّیْٓ اَعُوْذُ بِكَ مِنْ اَنْ اُشْرِكَ بِكَ شَيْئًا وَّاَنَآ اَعْلَمُ بِهٖ وَ اَسْتَغْفِرُكَ لِمَا لَآ اَعْلَمُ بِهٖ تُبْتُ عَنْهُ وَ تَبَرَّأْتُ مِنَ الْكُفْرِ وَ الشِّرْكِ وَ الْكِذْبِ وَ الْغِيْبَةِ وَ الْبِدْعَةِ وَ النَّمِيْمَةِ وَ الْفَوَاحِشِ وَ الْبُهْتَانِ وَ الْمَعَاصِىْ كُلِّهَا وَ اَسْلَمْتُ وَ اَقُوْلُ لَآ اِلٰهَ اِلَّا اللهُ مُحَمَّدٌ رَّسُوْلُ اللهِؕ</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="qalma_list_trans">
        <item>There is none worthy of worship but Allah, Muhammad [peace be upon him] is the messenger of Allah.</item>
        <item>I bear witness that (there is) no god except Allah; One is He, no partner hath He, and I bear witness that Muhammad (Sall-Allahu Alayhi wa Sallam) is His Servant and Messenger.</item>
        <item>Flawless is Allah and the Praise is of Allah, and (there is) no god except Allah, and Allah is the Greatest. And (there is) neither might nor power except with Allah, the Sublime, the Tremendous.</item>
        <item>(There is) no god except Allah - One is He, no partners hath He. His is the Dominion, and His is the Praise. He gives life and causes death, and He is Living, who will not die, never. He of Majesty and Munificence. Within His Hand is (all) good. And He is, upon everything, Able (to exert His Will).</item>
        <item>"I seek forgiveness from Allah, my Lord, from every sin I committed knowingly or unknowingly, secretly or openly, and I turn towards Him from the sin that I know and from the sin that I do not know. Certainly You, You (are) the knower of the hidden things and the Concealer (of) the mistakes and the Forgiver (of) the sins. And (there is) no power and no strength except from Allah, the Most High, the Most Great".</item>
        <item>"O Allah! I seek protection in You from that I should not join any partner with You and I have knowledge of it. I seek Your forgiveness from that which I do not know. I repent from it (ignorance) and I reject disbelief (kufr) and joining partners with You (shirk) and of falsehood and slandering (gheebat) and innovation in religion (bid'at) and tell-tales (nameemat) and bad, evil deeds (fawahish) and the blame and the disobedience, all of them. I submit to Your will and I believe and I declare: There is none worthy of worship except Allah and Muhammad( Peace Be Upon On Him) is His Messenger."</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="txtSehri">Pассвет</string>
    <string name="txtIftar">питание</string>

</resources>